[{
        "Question": "Select question to ask",
        "Answer": ""
},{
        "Question": "What do you see?",
        "Answer": "A large block is below the medium block. A green loc_b location is below the small block. A blue loc_c location is below the large block. A medium block is on the large block. A small block is on the green loc_b location. A large block is on the blue loc_c location. I see a green loc_a location."
}, {
        "Question": "What is on the blue location?",
        "Answer": "A large block"
}, {
        "Question": "What is on the large block?",
        "Answer": "A medium block"
}, {
        "Question": "What is the volume of the large block?",
        "Answer": "The volume is 3.0 ."
}, {
        "Question": "What is the volume of the small block?",
        "Answer": "The volume is 1.0 ."
}, {
	"Question": "Describe the small block?",
        "Answer": "The size is small. The volume is 1.0 . A green loc_b location is below the small block."
}, {
	"Question": "Describe the medium block?",
        "Answer": "The size is medium. The volume is 2.0 . A large block is below the medium block. "
}, {
	"Question": "Describe the large block?",
        "Answer": "The size is large. The volume is 3.0 . A blue loc_c location is below the large block. A medium block is on the large block. "
}, {
	"Question": "Describe the blue location?",
        "Answer": "The color is blue. The volume is 4.0 . A large block is on the blue loc_c location."
}, {
        "Question": "What is 'clear'?",
        "Answer": "If an object is not below an object , then it is clear."
    },]

